{
    "subject": "resource/Solar_Turbines",
    "predicate": "property/services",
    "object": "resource/Training",
    "human_readable": "Solar Turbines provides training services.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9577290415763855,
            "question": "Does Solar Turbines provide training?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9454944133758545,
            "question": "How might Solar Turbines promote their training services?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9173485040664673,
            "question": "What industries could benefit from Solar Turbines' training services?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.912285566329956,
            "question": "Why might a company offer training services like Solar Turbines?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9117434620857239,
            "question": "Who are the likely recipients of Solar Turbines' training services?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8714872002601624,
            "question": "What kind of services does Solar Turbines offer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8058509826660156,
            "question": "What skills or knowledge could individuals gain from Solar Turbines' training?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7993290424346924,
            "question": "What are the potential benefits of receiving training from Solar Turbines?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7880426049232483,
            "question": "What area might Solar Turbines specialize in based on the service they provide?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4486578106880188,
            "question": "Can you think of other companies that provide similar training services?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Solar Turbines provides training services.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6713_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What area might Solar Turbines specialize in based on the service they provide?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6713_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the potential benefits of receiving training from Solar Turbines?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6713_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What skills or knowledge could individuals gain from Solar Turbines' training?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6713_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6713_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6713_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6713_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6713_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6713_129.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6713_137.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6713_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6713_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6713_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6713_76.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention GRID's Training Philosophy and describe their training programs in detail. Additionally, the text from file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6713/re-ranker-msmarco/105.txt mentions the Solar Turbines' Training Academy, which provides students with valuable insight on engineering application in industry. This suggests that Solar Turbines does provide training services, making the triple correct according to the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe context information mentions the \"Solar Turbines CLC Training Academy Coordinators\" and their role in providing educational insights to students, which supports the statement that Solar Turbines provides training services."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}